Visit turkision.com for more!
How is this going to end, brother?
It's obvious how it is going to end, brother.
It's obvious.
Come on, let's go to father.
I was right.
But what I did was wrong.
I will live what's in my destiny.
I will either live to see another day...
...or die.
Oh, Boran Bey on one side...
...and Konur Bey on the other.
May Allah help our brothers.
Peace be with you, Konur Bey.
Peace be upon you.
We came to pick you up for Divan.
It's my Bey’s order, konur bey.
Come on.
It's hurting us, too.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey.
Father, if you excuse us, we want to talk to you.
About Konur Bey and Boran Bey.
You will learn what's going to happen
together with everyone else at the divan.
Father.
Konur Bey is the head of the army.
And Boran Bey is your confidante. Your brother.
They served you for years.
Is this how it's going to end?
If the head of the army causes trouble...
...and my brother...
...can't control his nafs...
...then what’s going to happen to Kayi’s army?
What’s going to happen to Kayi's people?
A little spark that...
...can burn the great plane tree.
I won't let anyone burn that great plane tree!
Now...
...they will pay...
...for what they have done.
It’s time to make a decision now.
Peace and mercy of Allah be upon you.
I made a mistake, oh Allah.
I did something that does not suit me.
Forgive me, allow me to make up for my mistakes.
May Allah give strength to our brothers.
In the name of Allah.
Peace be with you.
May Allah accept it Boran Bey.
May Allah accept it.
Allah bless you brothers.
Bey asked to get you for the divan.
Time is here.
None of us..
...wanted this to happen Boran Bey.
Osman Bey...
...will be merciful I hope.
I hope so.
Boran.
We’re incomplete without you.
Baysungur.
My brave brother.
Tell me.
We can't control what happens right?
Yes.
I made a mistake.
I'll pay for it.
Come on.
Don't make my Bey wait.
Okay then.
Come on.
Praise be, my girl. They're beautiful.
Good job to your late mother.
They're all made by her.
So they're precious.
I wish she could have seen this.
I wish my sweet girl.
They're my father's most trusted Beys.
His closest soldiers.
Laws are clear Fatma Hatun.
Tribesman who injure another will die for it.
There was blood.
I wish what's best will come true.
Justice is a balance between punishment and mercy.
Osman Bey will make the right choice.
I hope so.
Look at that.
They're preparing for court.
Tribe's going crazy.
His most trusted men had a fight.
I might not even have to interfere.
They'll destroy each other.
There's no point of staying here.
Attention!
Osman Bey!
In The name of Allah, the merciful, the beneficent.
We're holding this divan..
...for Konur Bey's and...
...Boran Bey's crimes.
May Allah...
May Allah allow us to give the right rule.
Amen.
Ameen.
Step up.
Blood must not be spilled between...
...soldier who fight back
to back on the battlefield.
It can't.
It can’t.
One...
...is the commander of the army...
...the head of the alps, Konur Bey.
The other...
...is the one who I trust...
...even my family with...
...Boran Bey.
Do you have anything to say?
In our customs...
...the punishment for an alp drawing
out a knife on the other is decided.
I am the one who drew a knife first.
I'll accept your rule without a sound, my bey.
Do you have anything to say?
I'm the one who caused things to get like this.
It has gotten this far because of me.
I'm ready to pay for it, my bey.
You understand it..
But it's too late.
A horseshoe carries a horse.
A horse carries a soldier.
And a soldier...
..carries the whole army.
You were the heads of the army.
But..
...what you did was disturbing the order.
I would never...
...allow the order of the
Kayi's army to be disturbed.
Kayi’s army to be disturbed.
A nation..
...cannot thrive in disorder.
...cannot thrive in individuality.
You were careless.
The only thing that will wake you up from this...
...is death.
But I know that..
...you don't fear dying.
Death doesn't scare you.
Death...
...is not a punishment for you.
We have our rule now.
You'll be exiled.
You will be away from your tribe, your
beloved ones, and most importantly...
...from ghaza.
That will be the greatest punishment for you.
Now, as for the new duties.
You will lead the army now, Orhan Bey.
May Allah allow me to be successful.
Yenisehir and the tribes are now
in your management, Alaeddin Bey.
As you command, my Bey.
And you will take..
...Boran bey’s place, Cerkutay.
From now on, you will be the one...
...to stand right next to me.
As you command my Bey.
Speak Solgur Aga.
My Bey, Imren sent word.
He found where the Catalans
are, they entered our lands.
Alright, alright.
Neither Catalans nor Frenks..
...we won’t let any of them enter our lands.
Cerkutay.
Orhan.
Prepare the army quickly.
With the help of Allah, we will go after them.
As you command, my Bey.
As you command my Bey.
Malhun, it's getting more dangerous.
We are losing the men from inner circle.
Even if we are few...
...we have no other choice but to resist, Bala.
My Bey.
I know you exiled us...
...but while the situation is like this..
...don’t keep us away from ghaza.
Please, my Bey.
At least allow us to join the ghaza, my Bey.
No!
Your biggest punishment...
...will be to stay away from ghaza.
Now...
...you will turn in your weapons, Beylic rings...
...your seals...
...to the clerk.
And after that..
...get out of my tribe.
As you command my Bey.
Don't show any mercy to those damn Catalans
who attacked Jesus' army from behind!
Cardinal, don’t worry.
What I am going to do to them will
bring fear to the enemies of the crusaders.
But first, I will learn why they betrayed.
Someone must be behind this.
Long live Osman Bey.
It's a fire!
Come quick!
Bring water!
It's a fire!
Tent's on fire!
Bring water!
The dowry won't bring you peace.
It'll bring suffering.
It'll burn like hell.
Exile has rules Konur Bey.
You must leave behind...
...the sword symbolizing
titles, honor and brotherhood.
My Bey ordered so.
As my Alaeddin Bey wishes.
You raised us with your training Konur Bey.
Know that this pains us too.
Don't.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Konur Bey.
We’ll take the armor too.
As Alaeddin Bey wishes.
Give me your blessing.
We do.
May Allah help you with your path.
May Allah protect you.
May Allah protect you too.
May-Allah help you Konur Bey.
May Allah protect you.
May Allah help you.
The dagger was my Bey's gift.
I regret that I have to give my Bey's gift.
We can see it in your eyes Boran.
After all these years..
...after all the dinners we shared...
...is this how you'd end up leaving Boran?
My Bey orders...
...and we obey, Bala Hatun.
May Allah protect you.
May Allah protect you too Boran.
May Allah help you.
Thank you.
What will you do now? Where will you go?
I don't know anything but to serve my bey.
I'll continue to serve him.
I'll tell everyone about my magnificent Osman Bey.
May Allah let you have an easy journey, Boran Bey.
Different paths...
...but the same. goal.
We will meet again.
If Allah permits.
May Allah protect you all.
Have a safe journey.
You're going to go the
opposite direction, Boran Bey.
You won't come across Konur Bey.
Thank you my Shahzade.
Alright.
May Allah protect you.
-May Allah protect you.
-May Allah protect you Boran Bey.
-Have a safe journey.
Have a safe journey.
May Allah protect you.
-May Allah protect you.
-Have a safe journey.
May Allah protect you.
This chest will be your hell.
Come here.
I'm going to eat you for iftar, don't run.
I'm going to catch you. Come here.
Goat..
I'll have you for iftar.
Where did he come from?
Where are you?
You ran away well.
But I'm going to find you.
Found you.
So you're there...
Come here. I'll have you for iftar.
I heard that two of your most trusted men fought.
I hope that you didn’t get hurt.
. Were you betrayed like me?
There wasn't any betrayal.
You should worry about your traitors.
Worry about the Catalans.
Catalans are close.
As we talked before, I set up the traps.
Come on.
To your positions.
AS you command, my Bey.
Come on alps.
Now..
Tell your man to call the commander.
Kanyumaz, I thought you were dead.
I am not dead, but soon I will be caught.
Osman is looking for the spy. Where is Imren Tegin?
I have important news for him.
Imren Tegin is not here, tell me instead.
Where are my child and my
hatun? I want to see them first.
Kanyumaz! You don't learn your lesson, do you?
Tell me what you know first.
Alaeddin Bey and Mehmet Bey.
They made a deal to take border
bazaar back. They will attack soon.
Osman.
You showed your true colors!
I will inform Imren Tegin about this.
What's going on here?
Is there anyone?
Fire! The tent is on fire!
Bring water quickly!
The tent is on fire!
Mother!
Is there anyone?
Bring water!
The dowry! My mother left them to me!
Mother! Is there anyone out there!?
Oh Allah, protect me.
Mother
Mother!
Gazi?
Hold on Gazi!
Is there anyone out there?
Oh Allah help me.
Gazi, wait.
What's happening here?
We heard Gazi, Elcim Hatun went inside.
Gazi?
Pour water! Put out the fire!
Come on!
I am coming!
You are okay, right? We will get out now.
We will get out of here. Come.
Hold onto me.
Don't let go.
Alps, Come on!
Ghazi
Bring water now! Come on!
Come on! Bring water
Elcim! Elcim!
Mother.
Sweetie it's okay.
Ghazi
Are you okay my boy?
Ghazi are you okay?
Come on!
I'm here sweetie.
Ghazi.
Bring water!
Sweetie.
Come on!
Ghazi.
Ghazi
Sweetie.
I'm fasting!
My boy's fasting.
My boy's fasting. Okay.
I'm here sweetie.
Come on brother!
Alps! Put it out now!
Come on!
Elcim Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Your hands are burnt.
It's okay. Ghazi.
Ghazi are you okay?
Allah bless you.
You saved my son.
Do not even mention it.
Anyone would do the same.
No they wouldn’t.
You're so brave..
...that you didn't care for your own life.
But we must get your hands checked.
It hurts.
-It's going to be okay.
The dowry is gone.
My mother left them to us.
How did this happen?
It’s okay, as long as we're safe.
It's not more important than Ghazi.
He's okay.
Malhun Hatun.
We were going to take supplies to Sogut.
Let's not be late.
Not now my girl. You stay. I'll go.
It’s not important. I'll come.
My girl.
You go. We'll protect here.
Okay then. Let's go.
Take it.
Come on sweetie.
Come on.
Let's go.
Bring water!
Catalan commander. Brave Andor.
Imren Tegin awaits you.
Let's go see him.
I wonder what Imren will say.
Imren Tegin.
What is going in that mind of yours
which had fooled Olcay Tuhan before?
Why did you call me here?
I didn't.
My partner wanted to talk face
to face with the Catalan dogs.
What? Partner?
Welcome to the Turks' land, commander.
But you won't be staying here for long.
Who are you?
Your executioner.
What does this mean Imren?
These lands you've stepped on will be-your end.
Alps, attack
Allah is the Greatest!
Wait.
Now.
Now you're in the palms of our hands.
Allah.
Come on brothers.
Allah is the Greatest!
-Allah is the Greatest!
Why did you betray us?
What are you talking about?
We do not ask questions to traitors.
We just severe their heads from their bodies.
He got what he deserved.
Good work.
How much is this?
What is it Boran Bey?
Is there no more bows in Osman Bey's
post that you're buying one from me?
Are you selling it or not, tell me that.
20 silver coins, my bey.
Okay.
Show me your swords too.
What about the horseshoes?
I just put them on, you'll be
using them for a long time.
Thank you.
Here, thank you.
Peace be with you.
Good day.
Thanks, my Bey. Welcome.
Show me your best sword.
My Bey, I forged this myself. It has
two gutters. This is my best sword.
My Bey, the victory is ours. We
defeated all of them Alhamdulillah.
Thank you, you got a great victory, son.
Thank you my Bey.
Well done.
Your son is brave just like you, Osman Bey.
Your father Ertugrul...
...Ghazi.
Watch it!
Don't casually utter his name!
Didn't he obey Seljuk state, too?
During the time of Seljuk
state, the Turks were glorious.
Can't you pledge loyalty to me and stand behind me?
The times changed.
While you were betraying
others, we made our lands bigger.
Don't have such futile dreams.
But if you still want to be united..
..here, kiss my hand, and
I will accept your pledge.
So this unity will always be a dream, huh?
Yeah.
What if the people you trust betray you too?
What will you do then?
I will bring the new comers to Border bazaar.
I don't want any rebels in my castle.
Ambassadors in Atranos and the
Cardinal will go to border bazaar too.
It will bring courage to the soldiers.
Not at a time like this.
Orhan and alps will accompany them.
As you command, my Bey.
Take good care of my Cardinal, Orhan!
Come on alps!
Before they realize what’s
happening, we will take them down.
Everyone knows what to do. Come on.
Alright my Bey.
We gained a great victory together.
When are you going to tell
me the location of my relics?
When the crusaders get out of my lands...
...you will take your relics.
Those who come will be
destroyed eventually, Osman Bey.
But if this goes on, this
campaign will last longer.
What's the hurry?
I could buy the necessities. I wish you
had stayed back there, Holofira Hatun.
Holofira is dead, Kismet.
Holofira is no more.
Malhun Hatun is coming!
Welcome Malhun Hatun
Thank you!
Elcim Hatun is with her. It
will end badly if they see you.
What are they doing here?
Thank you.
Why did they come?
Let's leave, Holofira Hatun, they will see us.
He tricked me.
He made me kill the Catalans!
That dog is telling Imren something.
Let's be on alert. We have to leave here.
As you command my Bey.
Prepare the horses.
Alps.
Osman!
You acted as my ally!
You attacked the Frenks, too, right?
Now you understand.
You found the Frenks.
You made me kill Catalans.
Now you sent your son after Cardinal messengers.
Osman!
What kind of a game is this?
I'll kill you right here.
Soldiers!
Will you disregard messengers and relics?
You set this plan to save your lands.
In return...
...I will burn this land with the crusaders.
I won't let them pass!
And you can't hurt me.
We’ll go on until one of us die.
Let's go.
Then..
...you'll breathe until you
tell me where the relics are.
First, your son who went
after the cardinals will die.
Orhan dies!
Daniel.
Sent your best men.
Bring me Orhan's head.
They'll kill all the Alps.
Osman will have iftar...
..with his son's head.
As you wish Imren Tegin.
Take position!
Alright then.
Cerkutay.
My Bey.
I guess we'll reach shahada side by side.
Dying by your side is an honor my Bey.
But one of us...
...must send word to Orhan.
Osman!
The one next to you will die first.
Everyone who knows your name will die.
Will you keep waiting?
We’ll chase these dogs into the forest.
We’ll kill them one
by one like wolves.
Attack!
Release the horses!
Allah bless you.
All of us, if Allah permits.
Osman Bey sent his regards.
Allah bless you.
Ramadan Mubarak!
My girl.
Come.
You'll be in pain if you move it.
Stay still until it gets better.
Thank Allah..
...He protected us from worse situations.
Ghazi is alright.
I was so scared when I saw him in flames.
That fear.... My girl...
Know that fear well..
When you have a child, you’ll
spend your life with that fear.
When I lost my mother...
...I thought I'd never have
anyone else in her place.
You're a mother to me.
You're a daughter to me, my girl.
I won't worry anymore.
Orhan and you will protect each other.
Keep respecting each other.
May your respect bear love.
I hope so Malhun Hatun.
Then, stop calling me Hatun.
Mother Malhun.
That's right.
Come my girl. Come here.
I know it's not like your mother's dowry...
...but Sogut's Hatuns are good at it.
They really are pretty.
Right. They are.
Come on.
Let's get you new dowry.
Come here Imren. Come here.
Give me the flying fire.
My Bey.
Come on! Come on!
Alps! Make them retreat!
We’ll turn these dogs into birds and they'll fly.
Or they’ll surround us.
Don't you worry.
We’ll make them fly like thirds.
Imren Tegin will be gone like he deserves.
Orhan is in danger. We have to go to him.
They're going to take flight.
Alps.
Take cover.
Kill them all.
Come here Imren.
Let's see how well you fly.
My bey, they're coming.
They're coming closer.
Alps, come on.
Brother, come.
Come on brother.
Come on.
Bring the horses.
No one will leave this forest alive.
It hurts, Gonca Hatun, it hurts. It hurts so much.
It hurts, Gonca Hatun.
Poor soul, look at him...
I didn't even touch it yet, Ghazi.
You can't stand pain at all.
Right Gonca Hatun?
Don't you see that huge wound Alaeddin Bey?
Ghazi is holding on so well, he's so brave.
He's jealous of me, my Gonca.
You...
All of my mother's work is gone.
There's nothing left.
How did that fire start?
How did you burn down that tent?
What will we do now?
I didn't burn it, mother.
I was chasing that goat.
I went inside that tent and
someone hit me on the head.
I just fell to the ground.
Who hit you?
Who could it be? He must be lying.
I swear I'm not.
Come here.
He has a bump.
Who hit you, did you see?
I didn't.
But they are a coward.
They attacked me from the back.
Such a brave kid.
Why would anyone want to burn down the dowery?
Ghazi.
Could it be that you hit your head?
I swear they hit me.
You're right, he must be saying
these things because of the shock.
Okay Ghazi.
You did something, just own up to it and apologize.
Okay Ghazi's mother.
I believe you Ghazi.
The horses rested for enough.
We still have a long way to go to Atranos.
Alps.
Something’s happening.
Be cautious and get ready.
What are you whispering about?
Tell us so we know too.
We’re talking about your betrayal.
Osman Bey's betrayal.
But he is paying for it with his life now.
Just like you.
Father...
Soldiers.
Alps.
I'll be the one killing you.
Attack.
Allah is the Greatest!
Oh Allah!
Hold on my Bey! We are coming!
Come on alps!
Come on Cerkutay.
We will split in two here.
Cerkutay, we have no horses, and no
time. We need to inform Orhan quickly.
He will be informed, my Bey.
Thank you.
Don't worry, you will be okay.
Alright my Bey.
3 alps will accompany Cerkutay Bey.
Come on brothers. Hold on.
The rest is with me.
Those who want to die come face us, huh?
Come here!
Come on alps!
My shahzade, aren't we going to help them?
Helping him and not helping
him, both are problems for me.
If Orhan dies, Osman will be left alone.
And that will be useful for me.
My shahzade!
Hold on alps! Osman Bey is waiting for us!
You came right on time, Mehmet Bey!
We are going to kill that dog
Imren together, Orhan Bey.
Allah is the Greatest!
Come here!
You have nowhere fo escape,
Osman, stop making plans.
I am not running away.
I was just planning how to kill you.
Come here!
Hang on brother.
Hang on.
Hang on brother. Hang on.
Alps!
Hang on brother.
End of the road, Cerkutay.
Have some rest.
You're lucky.
You'll die before Osman.
No.
You're the lucky man.
Because you'll die by my hand.
To get to Osman Bey...
...you have crush me first.
Then I will.
Attack!
They found Osman.
They're going to Yildiz Kaya.
Take me to him.
I want him alive.
My Bey.
The Righteous
Praise be.
You hit the target each time Fatma.
Well... I better do it brother.
I train all the time.
The Righteous
Praise be my sister.
What will you do about Gonca?
Will you do what my brother did, will you...
-Don't say it sister.
I go crazy when I hear
someone else's name beside hers.
I don't even know what I'll do if I see her...
...with someone else.
If you do nothing and wait here...
...the day will come soon.
I know what to do sister.
I won't let you go trickster Hatun.
I won't let you go.
Gonca.
Gohca just wait and listen to me.
You and I are two separate rivers.
Now we meet again.
You and I can't-be separated now Gonca.
We are one.
Alaeddin.
You know what would happen.
-We cannot fight this war -Why not?
Why not?
You and I agreed to fight together.
You are willing to fight all?
And your father and mother?
Will you be able to stand against them Alaeddin?
What don't you understand?
They don't trust me.
Gonca.
I made a promise to you.
Do you remember?
I'll always be with you.
No.
You can't leave them.
I won't leave you
either Gonca, I won't.
You're my home.
You're my first love.
As long as'this soul is in this body...
...you will be my only love.
Madrasah student...
Look, just say you want this...
...then I'll talk with my father.
Just say yes and I'll talk with Yakup
Bey, I've thought about all of that.
But..
...give me an answer first.
...we have to go against our families...
...will you be able to give up on
everything and say yes to me Gonca?
Madrasah student...
I'm ready to fight for this love...
...but...
-There is no but.
There is no but Gonca..
I have only one chance.
Are you in...
...or out?
I'm in.
I am in.
I'll walk this path with you.
-Gonca.
-No matter the ending, madrasah student.
-Alaeddin.
Come on.
Go talk with Osman Bey.
I'll go...But...
...don’t change your mind again.
-No.
-Okay.
Then give me a promise of love.
Will you swear on all the love stories?
I swear on all the love stories.
Gonca.
Okay.
I'll go and talk with my father then.
Go on.
i'll go.
I'll go Gonca.
Gonca.
Allah...
Thank Allah...
Gonca.
Allah.
Thank Allah.
I will go and talk with my father.
I told you there was nowhere to run Osman.
Cerkutay died.
Your alps died.
And finally...
...your son, Shahzade Orhan.
He died too.
The only reason you're alive is my relics.
If not you'd be dead already.
Forget touching my son...
..you can't even cut my beard.
I'm going to kill you in such a way...
In such a way...
You're resisting for nothing Osman.
Resisting comes from belief.
I'll never surrender.
I'm going to kill you in such a way...
In such a way...
I hope it's nothing bad.
Bala Hatun, Malhun Hatun.
What is it?
Imren's men learned the
plan. They attacked Orhan Bey.
What are you saying?
Mehmet Bey saved shahzade
Orhan the last minute, but...
...Osman Bey is in a tough position.
They are attacking from all sides.
What?
Bala!
Alps! Sisters! To horses! We
are going to support Osman Bey!
Come on!
Bring me my sword!
I won't leave you alone, mother!
No, Alaeddin. Stay here.
The infidels,will come for our cities.
Your duty here is more important.
Your father entrusted the tribe to you.
May Allah protect you.
Come on.
Oh Allah, protect them.
Oh Allah, don't let my people suffer...
...from losing their Bey, and don't
let me suffer from losing my father.
My shahzade, Osman Bey
and Cerkutay Bey were not there.
It's impossible that they know
about Osman Bey’s move.
My shahzade, there is something else going on.
Well, they are bastards, after all.
They need no reason to attack Osman Bey.
Someone told Imren about our move.
There is a traitor among us.
I will find that traitor!
I will find him and punish him!
But first..
...first we will find Osman Bey.
They released the horses to escape, my shahzade.
Imren will not leave their
trail before he gets the relics.
We will find my father before that dog
My shahzade, there are traces here!
They lead to the forest.
Move away!
We won’t stop until we find
them. Everyone, to your horses!
We won’t stop until we find Osman Bey! Come on!
Imren Tegin, or whatever your name is!
Come here!
Stop.
Don't interfere.
He is mine.
Capture him!
You are'gping with my relics,. Osman.
The end of an era!
Make sure he's dead.
Allah protect him.
Cerkutay Bey! Cerkutay Bey!
Cerkutay.
Cerkutay! Brother!
Bring me a cloth! Come on!
Cerkutay. Brother open your eyes!
Open your eyes!
What will we do my shehzade?
He'll be okay!
Come on!
My Bey.
This will stop the bleeding.
You'll be okay.
My Bey.
Tell me.
Tell me Cerkutay Bey.
Bey save yourself.
My Bey. They’re after you!
Tell me.
Where's my father?
Yildiz....
Yildiz Cave?
Don't tire yourself Cerkutay Bey.
Don't tire yourself.
Baysungur.
-Shehzade?
Take Cerkitay Bey to the tribe.
Alaeddin will help him Allah willing.
Take him. Keep pressure on the wound.
As you wish my Shehzade.
Come on.
In the name of Allah.
-Brother.
You'll be okay.
Cerkutay doesn't die!
Cerkutay!
Hang on brother.
You'll be okay. You'll be okay.
Cerkutay.
Hang on brother.
You'll be okay. You’ll be okay.
My Bey.
Father!
Osman Bey!
Osman Bey isn't here.
He killed these dogs and kept moving.
Father!
Shehzade.
My Bey's sword.
They dragged my Bey with a horse.
Then he dropped his sword.
Allah protect my Bey.
What if Osman Bey died?
Shut up!
Get it together.
My father won't easily die!
We’ll follow the trail.
We’ll find Osman Bey. Come on!
Shehzade Alaeddin!
Come on.
-Baysungur.
Cerkutay’s wounded.
Cerkutay!
He'll be okay.
Shehzade!
Alps!
-Shehzade Alaeddin!
Cerkutay Bey!
Hang on!
-Carry him!
Ulgen.
Father
-Ghazi.
-Don't leave us.
He's gone...
My bey...
My bey is gone...
Osman.
My bey...
Boil water quickly. Come on.
Ghazi.
Father
I'm with you.
Hold on Cerkutay Bey.
Take him to infirmary quickly.
-My Shahzade.
-Come on.
Heal my father.
-Heal him.
-He's going to be okay.
Stand straight.
I promise you, I'm going to heal him okay?
Come on.
Orhan.
Thank Allah, you're okay.
We’re okay, Alhamdulillah mother Bala.
Son, your father. Where is Osman Bey?
My father.
He's not here mother Bala.
We followed the trails, they
dragged him with a horse.
But we will find him with Allah’s permission.
We will.
Where did you go?
Where should we go now?
We came from this way, Bala Hatun.
But the trail goes that way.
Okay, we'll separate then.
You go there, we will go this way.
One who finds him should shoot an whistle arrow.
Okay, come on son.
Come on.
Iltutan?
Osman.
Son.
Iltutan, what happened son?
Stop son.
Are you looking for Osman Bey too?
Son?
Where is Osman Bey?
Where is he?
Okay, son okay we'll find him. Come on.
Come on, take me to him. Come on.
Come on. Allah..
Allah, spare him.. Come on son.
Come on, to your horses.
Come on.
Come on lltutan.
Come on son.
Osman.
My bey. Osman.
He's alive. You're alive thank Allah.
Take it off, slowly.
Slowly.
My bey.
Osman...Slow.
Thank Allah.
Bring water, come on.
Water...Osman...
Osman.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm okay...
Orhan.
Alps.
How are they?
They are all okay.
Don't worry.
If everyone is okay...
...then why are you crying?
Why are you crying? I told you.
You can't get rid of me easily.
Well, who wants to get rid of you, huh?
But you love scaring us. You scared us again.
Thank Allah your armor protected
you. But you are wounded.
Well, Allah has helped me survive.
But we defeated Imren.
Bala, there is a traitor among us.
He exposed us.
We will find the traitor, my Bey.
Like the first day.
You saved me.
The first time I saw you, you
were a Bey’s son, covered in mud.
Now you are covered in mud again...
...but we have tall children.
Like the first day.
Your smile is still the same.
Osman.
They are coming.
Come on.
Come on, Bala.
Bala, we talked about the past.
Now the history repeats itself, huh?
That's right.
Come here!
-Are you okay Bala?
-Yeah.
Okay.
-Son.
-My Bey!
My Bey.
Are you okay?
-I am okay, don’t worry.
-Thank Allah.
Osman Bey.
Where is Cerkutay?
My Bey, Cerkutay Bey is heavily wounded.
We sent him to the tribe to get treated.
Don't let anything happen to Cerkutay.
If it’s not Cerkutay, then who saved you?
Mehmet Bey.
It would be really tough for
us if he had not come in time.
Thank you, thank you Mehmet Bey.
Thank you.
Prepare your alps.
We will take the border market.
Thank you Osman Bey, it's about time.
Osman Bey, someone was protecting us.
It’s obvious who it was. Boran.
Even exile did not stop him. He acts alone.
We will see. Lets go.
Come on.
Peace be with you Boran Bey.
Peace be upon you.
You look like you return from defeat. What's wrong?
You see through me Yunus Emre.
You're right.
It was a defeat.
It was such a big defeat...
...that my enemy's defeated...
...and so am I.
The infidel..
...can cut through skin.
But a fight with a brother injured the soul.
Brother...
The man I call my brother...
...angered me so much.
He talked bad about my service.
I couldn't help it.
I am...
-You are...
...Osman Bey's closest man...
...his most loyal man.
What he said hurt you.
And if you never said a word back...
...you'd be uncomfortable.
You didn’t want to look weak.
And you thought 'Who is he that he can say it?'
This is arrogance.
Arrogance and anger...
...confuses man's mind...
...and makes him...
...face many troubles in the end.
One time..
...you asked of Omer Hadrath's anger.
I told you. Now I can tell you...
...about his justice and how
he quieted his arrogance.
Would you want that Boran Bey?
Omer Hadrath..
...during his caliph era...
...asked his people in khutbe.
’If I left Allah's word...
..what would you do?'
A companion answered him.
Td fix you with my sword, Omer.'
Omer Hadrath was happy to hear it.
He opened his hands...
...and tells Allah...
...'Allah...
...thank You...
...for if I ever forget Your Word...
...and ignore Your Justice..
...there are people who'll
fix me with their sword.'
Men will make mistakes.
But what matters is to see the truth...
...and make amends.
Say Tawba...
...and wait for forgiveness.
Now you said...
...the fight had no victor.
Anger and arrogance...
...defeated you and your brother.
If you don't let you of arrogance...
...and prioritize your brother...
...the fight's victor will never change.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
It's your fault our innocent
soldiers died Imren Tegin.
How could you be fooled?
Everything will be okay Cardinal.
How will that be?
Imren Tegin.
Osman is alive.
He's going to his tribe.
You made a big mistake.
We lost.
You trusted Osman.
And you paid...
-Enough!
I'll give you everything I promised Cardinal.
Despite Osman?
Despite Osman.
I'll use Gunduz.
Osman can only be defeated by his loved ones.
I saw it.
So I'll take Gunduz.
Then I'll have my relics.
And I'll stop the two tribes uniting.
Imren Tegin.
Commander Konur Bey.
He was seen at the Yenisehir inn.
Good.
Konur and I share blood.
He's of Seljuk blood.
Do whatever you have to do and make him join us.
I'm going to land a hit on
Osman from this side too.
We made a mistake Holofira Hatun.
Let's go back before anyone sees us.
If someone sees us..
I know it's very dangerous Kismet.
But I can't just wait while Orhan is in danger.
I have to find out what happened.
Osman Bey is coming.
Welcome my bey.
Thank you.
-Allah spared you my bey.
-Get well soon my bey.
My bey.
Long live Osman Bey.
-Get well soon Osman Bey.
-Welcome my bey.
Get well soon my bey.
Father
Son.
Are you okay?
I was so scared thinking
something might happen to you.
I'm okay.
I'm okay my beautiful daughter.
Are you okay?
I'm okay mother, thank Allah.
Don't worry.
Thank Allah.
Brother.
You're okay right?
-I’m okay don't worry.
-Thank Allah my bey.
Father, are you okay?
Son.
Tell me.
How is Cerkutay?
He lost a lot of blood, father.
I dressed his wound.
I hope he's going to be okay.
I hope so, I hope so.
Baykurt.
My bey.
Bury our martyrs.
Check up on Cerkutay too.
Tell him to see me when he's better.
As you wish my bey.
Come on.
Holofira.
-Kismet we have to leave now.
-Holofira.
Holofira.
You risked so much coming here...
...but are you leaving without saying
a word to me, daughter of Tekfur?
I wanted to be sure that everyone was okay.
I was going to leave without seeing anyone.
Without being seen huh?
Which crowd can make blind
to your existence Holofira?
Even in pitch black darkness, I see your eyes.
Don't you know that?
God might have wanted us
to say goodbye one last time.
I loved you a lot.
I know you loved me too.
A lot.
I love you a lot too, daughter of Lord.
This love was a gift to us from God.
You won't be there anymore, yes...
...but this love will live
with me until my last breath.
Allah has written this in our...
...destiny instead of us being together...
If my heart is not shattered into pieces..
...it's because of my belief
in destiny, daughter of Tekfur.
Elcim Hatun is a good person.
She is fair. She is strong.
You will have children.
You will be a good Bey, and a good father.
You will be very happy.
And I will live knowing that.
Farewell now.
May your path be filled with roses.
May Allah protect you Lord's daughter.
Holofira.
Holofira!
I thought I was dreaming.
It’s you! You are alive!
Holofira! You are alive!
Gonca, no one can see me here.
I will tell you everything.
Thank you, I apprecite that.
Iftaar time is coming close.
May Allah accept.
Thanks.
I brought you Imren Tegin's regards.
If you excuse me, I have things to tell you.
Imren Tegin says that "Konur
Bey is from Seljuk lineage...
...and we are of the same blood."
Osman Bey was unfair to you.
Imren Tegin wants to see you by
his side to give you what’s your right.
What is it that's my right?
Imren Tegin will make you a commander.
When we take back Kite
castle, it will be your property.
But first you will come and
pledge loyalty to Imren Tegin.
You will take shelter in his castle, or...
There is no god but the one Allah!
Come on, in the name of Allah,
the merciful, the beneficent.
In the name of Allah, the merciful, the beneficent.
Go on, eat.
May Allah accept our fasting,
and the good deeds we do.
Amen.
May Allah help our family, those
who are in need, those who are sick...
...and to all Islam world.
May He treat them with His mercy.
Ameen, my Bey.
Ameen my Bey.
Come on.
The man of the tribe did his duty.
We defeated Catalans and Frenks.
We ruined Imren's plans. Now tell me.
What’s the situation with the dowry?
Well, despite some unpleasant
things, we prepared it.
We are taking care of what's necessary.
Before Boran Bey left, he sent
out messengers for the wedding.
As you said, we will accept
loyalty pledges as gifts.
Alright. We don't have much time left.
We don't have time, so...
...are the tents ready?
Yes, my Bey.
Thank you.
Let's take border bazaar tomorrow.
Then the ambassador and the Cardinal.
We will rid our lands from the infidels.
Then if Allah permits, we
will hold our wedding.
If Allah permits, my Bey.
Live long, Osman Bey.
You live long, too.
We will entrust the state that will
rule over the whole world, to you.
Enjoy.
I don't want it.
Cerkutay?
I'm here.
Who are you?
Ulgen.
Houri?
Do you still see Houri?
You're fighting for you life?
Get up! Get up!
Houri! Peace be with you.
What?
I'm Cerkutay.
Open your eyes I'll gauge them out Cerkutay.
I know you from somewhere.
Who is she? How do you know?
How?
Cerkutay!
You look so pretty.
You...
Cerkutay! Open your eyes! Now!
Praise be.
Praise be...
Cerkutay.
-Pretty.
I am your Hatun. I'll hit you
Ulgen.
You are prettier than all Houris.
I'll kill you myself. I'll do it.
Ulgen wait.
What? Who are those Houris?
I was dying. I almost died.
No you weren’t. I'll kill you Cerkutay. I'll do it.
Ulgen don't.
-Not yet!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm okay my Hatun.
Don't worry I'll be fine.
Cerkutay doesn't die.
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you.
Welcome. Welcome.
You honored us.
The Sultan of words, Yunus Emre.
Thank you.
You asked to welcome us in your tribe.
And we came.
If you break hearts...
...the prayer won't be accepted.
May Allah unite us.
Ameen. Thank you.
Amen. Amen.
You survived many traps.
May Allah accept it.
Thanks, thanks.
Well. Alps.
Yunus Emre and Dervishes are tired.
Come on. Bring them sherbet and water.
Welcome them.
Osman Bey.
Sherbet wets the throat.
It flushes away.
We...
...wish to wet the eyes and the heart if Allah permits.
We'd like to offer you gifts first.
Alright, alright.
Then welcome.
Know that there is no god but Allah.
There is no god but Allah.
-There is no god but Allah.
- I don't need this body but this soul...
-You need belief for the hereafter...
-There is no god but Allah.
There is no god but Allah.
-If you become one of Mohammed's ummah....
-There is no god but Allah.
-...you need speak about dhikr and Quran...
-Yunus who is filled with love...
-There is no god but Allah.
There is no god but Allah.
-Yunus who is filled with love...
-There is no god but Allah.
-It has no meaning without you...
There is no god but Allah.
There's a crowd out there.
People are coming in. It's just the time to leave.
Let's go.
I know about everything you did Olivia.
Is that so?
What did I do?
Don't be scared. I didn't come
here to make you confess.
After all, we both
want the same thing.
You're making me more curious.
Elcim and Orhan won't get married.
We will act together for this.
You're smarter than I thought you were.
For Holofira.
Stupid.
You can't even be my maid.
Now, we can go.
Great, Gracious Allah..
...bless Osman Bey and his army who have united...
...their hearts for
the fight of Islam, with
many victories just as
they were blessed today.
Amen.
Give them the power to
crush the heads of the Shirks.
Ameen.
For the sake of the martyrs
who died for the path...
...of Allah, and for Islam world, make
us followers of our prophet.
Amen.
Don't let us lose the righteous path.
Allow us to took shelter in Allah against...
...the people who tries to bring fitna among us.
Amen.
Oh Allah, allow the followers of
Mohammad to always have unity.
Amen.
Allow Osman Bey and his family
to carry the flag of our cause!
Amen.
Ameen.
Al Fatiha.
Oh Allah, glorify our prophet PBUH and his lineage!
Brother Hasan, they are going to runaway.
Inform shahzade.
I will leave marks on the path. Follow it.
Come on.
Thank you Oguz.
I hope this home will bring us peace.
I hope so.
Can I come in, Elcim Hatun?
Come in Orhan Bey.
Oh, praise be.
I came to see how you are.
I am fine. We were finishing last things.
The wedding is getting close,
we wanted to wrap things up.
You thought well.
I heard what you did for Gazi. You
jumped into the fire without hesitation.
Thank you.
You got wounded too.
This wound is nothing, Orhan Bey.
Yeah.
You will start talking about being a tribes girl.
But look, we are all in a tribe now.
You are in our care, Elcim Hatun.
I wouldn't want to be
embarrassed in front of your father.
My father knows that this is my tribe now.
Every life in the tribe is important for me.
I did what was necessary.
And I will continue to do so.
Thank you.
Can I come in, my shahzade?
Come in.
My shahzade, Olivia was going towards
the horses. They are gping to escape.
Oguz alp is following them to leave us marks.
We will let them escape.
They will think we did not realize it.
We will follow them..
...and learn the location of the secret passages.
I am coming too. I senses there
was something wrong with that Hatun.
And after what happened to my sister...
Don't get tired at this hour, Elcim hatun.
I am coming, Orhan Bey.
I am.
Who am I talking to?
Hasan, send word to alps.
Tell them to inform my father.
As you command my Shahzade.
Come on, in the name of Allah.
Kite area.
Where are you going Gunduz Bey?
I was coming to take your life, you dog!
Really? You talk too big for yourself.
I haven’t finished yet.
I am going to kill you and
hang your head on Kite castle.
Alps!
Not even your trusted Bey
Osman can take you from me.
Those who rule with cruelty...
....will have a miserable fate.
You'll end up dead too.
You're more important alive than dead.
Tell Osman I have Gunduz.
Now I have you Osman.
This is how we'll take control of border bazaar.
Gonca Hatun says..
...that Border Bazaar has some weaknesses.
Mehmet Bey said the same.
He behind these walls are some passage ways.
But..
...Imren must have reinforced them.
He increased watchers.
Is it just for the cardinal and the messenger?
Imren thinks...
...that the border bazaar...
...must be the base of crusaders.
Olcaytu's gold is in Border Bazaar.
That's why, Alaeddin Bey...
...Bala Hatun, Gonca Hatun...
....will go to scout the bazaar.
You'll see all the precautions.
Watch the guards and count them.
As you wish my Bey.
Then...
...we’ll take border bazaar...
...and the gold.
Tell Mehmet Bey to gather his Alps.
He'll meet us there.
Today is the last day of Turk's hospitality.
May Allah help us.
Amen.
Ameen my Bey.
You should have stayed at the tribe Hatun.
We rode horse all night long.
Why should I?
He's my enemy too.
was being kind.
I don't want you to be tired.
You should've stayed if you're tired.
I would come alone.
Allah help me.
You're such a stubborn Hatun.
You don't know me yet.
But..
..I don’t know you either.
We’ll meet Elcim Hatun.
We’ll have a lot of time for it.
Come on.
We’ll continue on foot from now on.
Tie up the horses Hasan.
Whats the situation Oguz?
They went that way S'hehzade.
Let's go.
Olivia.
Her plan...
...will cost her Atranos.
I hope so.
Osman Bey says after we
take Atranos he will hold a feast.
We will.
With Allah's permission once we take Atranos...
...despite Imren Tegin,
two Kayi tribes will unite...
...and hold that feast.
Come on.
Someone's coming.
Father
Elcim Hatun.
Calm down. We’ll wait for the right time.
Calm down. We'll wait for the right time.
Shout all you want Gunduz Bey.
No one can hear you here.
No one else knows about these passages but us.
No one.
Get him up.
Imren Tegin...
Father...
Attention, Osman Bey.
Alps.
Brave men.
Are you ready to take
what’s ours from the infidels?
We are my bey.
Oh praise be.
Come on then.
Osman Bey.
I have a message to you Osman Bey.
Tell me.
Imren Tegin took your Gunduz Bey.
you want him back..
...you're to go to
Atranos with the relics.
What are you saying?
Look here.
If you hurt Gunduz Bey...
...I'll make these lands your living hell.
Do you understand?
Do you?
Now get out of my sight.
Get out.
What will we do now my bey?
Border Bazaar...
...Atranos...
...or Gunduz Bey...
We won’t let any of our allies
to be prisoners of that infidel!
We are going to take his life.
We will never go back from our path
Never!
Visit turkision.com for more!